Janelle Vos

Web/software developer and IT professional dedicated to serving the online community better. Ready to take my coding skills to the next level. Hard Working and knowledgeable when it comes to various types of systems and understanding how to achieve the best end user experience possible by testing from a user perspective and then refining software based on that experience.

EXPERIENCE

Janelle codes, Roseville, CA — Web design

February 2014 - PRESENT

Built various web pages for my own website using ajax, php, javascript, CSS, and HTML5.

Planned website using SDLC method to achieve desired result.

Worked with end users to improve experience and develop features.

Consolidated communications, Roseville, CA — *Tech support II*

November 2015 - PRESENT

Developed various web pages for use by my tech support group using javascript, CSS, and HTML5.

Used the SDLC method to achieve the best possible outcome.

Work closely with co-workers and end users to refine features.

Worked with non-technical end users to get a better understanding of how to improve and/or educate users on how to utilize various features.

Trouble-shoot various technical issues with non-technical end users.

Document feedback from end users in order to improve.

Kept Knowledge base website up to date when new features, systems were added/changed or new network equipment/devices were added.

Sutter, Sacramento, CA — Tech support

August 2015 - October 2015

Trouble-shoot various technical issues with non-technical end users and educated and/or repaired various system features.

Documented results of interactions with end users to improve and maintain knowledge base.

Promptly repaired various issues where necessary, so end users (medical providers) could effectively perform patient treatment.

501 E street Roseville, CA 95678 (916) 856.7245 janelle@Janellasplace.com

SKILLS

Software development, SQL, C#, AWS, ASP.NET, Angular, Vue.js, SDLC, Javascript, NextJs, React, Prisma, CSS, HTML5, framer Motion, GitHub, Vercel, Clerk, Photoshop

AWARDS

Team player award outstanding student contributor

Referral from various customer complimenting my excellence in service

LANGUAGES

Javascript, HTML, CSS, Typescript

Nerds On Call, Charmichael, CA — *Tech support*

March 2015 - August 2015

Worked with end users in need of technical assistance for various systems and hardware.

Documented results and contributed where appropriate to the general knowledge base for ehow.com website.

EDUCATION

Heald College, Roseville — AAS

March 2003 - July 2005

I was taught best practice (SDLC) to build apps in .Net and Java with hands-on approach with real world examples, built and tested example apps and refined UI.

Learned industry standard approach to admin networks, repaired computers and Networks.

Received higher learning in GE- english, math, lit.

PROJECTS

Knowledge based website Wiki — website

Built and developed a website with another colleague with wiki how to pages for tier I support team to follow for reference

Gathered IT knowledge articles and information and merged it together in an easy to use and read website with multiple pages using Javascript, HTML and CSS

Social Media website — *website*

Developed a website where users can login and create a profile and post comments, friend other users, and/or comment on other users posts if they are friends and logged in.

React Profile — website

Profile page where potential employer can see my various projects and see my skill set when it comes to .NET, ASPNET, Angular, SQL, AWS, Vue.js, SDLC, Javascript, NextJs, React, Prisma, CSS, HTML5, framer Motion,